## CONTACT

Phone: 647-822-3042

E-mail: clement.sung7@gmail.com Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/clement-sung7

Site: <u>github.com/clembrulee</u> Portfolio: <u>clementsung.com</u>

#### PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- Javascript(ES6)
- React
- Firebase
- RESTful API
- jquery
- · Responsive design
- Website accessibility requirements
- Version control using Git and Github
- · Paired programming
- Team-based development
- Project Scope Management
- Microsoft Office(Word, Excel)
- Labware LIMS software
- Empower software

#### **ABOUT**

I am a front-end web developer with experience building web applications using HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Firebase and API integrations. My background as a quality control analyst has helped me develop adaptability, critical analysis, and attention to detail skills that I can apply to creating clean, responsive, and accessible web applications/solutions.

# **CLEMENT SUNG**

### FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

#### **PROJECTS**

## Podcast Prioritizer <u>Live / Code</u>

HTML |CSS| Javascript | React

Team development project created to recommend podcasts based on a user's travel destination

#### Hikari

Live / Code

#### HTML | CSS | Javascript | React

Anime TV show/Movie database/recommendation app created in react.

## Cratediggers Live / Code

HTML |SCSS| Javascript

Paired programming project created to recommend music artists based on similar artists or a specific genre

## **Captured**

Live / Code

HTML |SCSS

Photography themed multipage site created from PSD conversion

#### **EDUCATION**

WEB DEVELOPMENT IMMERSIVE BOOTCAMP // Juno College | Apr 2021 - June 2021

- 9 week immersive bootcamp (50+ hours /week)
- completed 7 projects
- paired programming and team development

JAVASCRIPT FUNDAMENTALS // Juno College | Feb 2021 - Mar 2021)

- 8 week part-time javascript course
- completed 2 projects in jquery

INTRO TO WEB DEVELOPMENT // Juno College | Oct 2021 - Nov 2021

- 8 week part-time web development course on HTML and CSS
- completed 2 projects

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN CHEMISTRY (BSC) Ryerson University | Sep 2010 - Apr 2015

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**QUALITY CONTROL ANALYST** 

Estee Lauder Companies Inc. | Dec 2019 - Mar 2021

- Performed analytical testing of in-process materials and raw materials on daily basis(10-15 samples per day) to meet release targets.
- Wrote comprehensive reports for out-of-specification results, deviations, and corrective and preventative action plans while managing time to perform daily analytical testing.
- Aided the team in daily routine instrument calibrations and analytical tests to maintain workflow.

#### QUALITY CONTROL CHEMIST

Apotex Inc | Feb 2016 - Dec 2019

- Performed analytical chemistry, and wet chemistry tests on various drug products, an average of 12 samples, on a daily basis
- Review chemists' documented work through LIMS(laboratory information management system) software prior to releasing the product to market.
- Worked in a QC lab following good manufacturing practices/good laboratory practices to adhere to regulatory bodies such as Health Canada and FDA and successfully completed 4+ audits